Guide to the Phillips Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Gendler, Joan (1923-2002) letter and invitation, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  Daughter of Samuel Rubinstein (1882-1927).
- Willey, Sharon (born 1956) letters and cards, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  Daughter of Joan Gendler (1923-2002).
- Sussman family
  - Sussman, David (circa 1849-1934) naturalization papers and passport, 1904-1907 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Passport was for a trip to Palestine (Jerusalem), with a visa from the Ottoman government, but was never used.
  - Sussman, Sol (1888-1959) obituary (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Sussman, Richard (born 1924) correspondence and other material, 2004-2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Son of Sol Sussman (1888-1959).